Explain this to me right now.
اشرح لي هذا الآن.
(Episode 110)
(الحلقة ١١٠)
Tell me why those two are still married!
أخبرني لماذا هذين الاثنين لا زالوا متزوجين!
Could you give us a moment, Director Min?
هل يمكن أن تعطينا لحظة، المخرج مين؟
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
Why haven't you filed the divorce papers yet?
لماذا لم تقدمي أوراق الطلاق حتى الآن؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Because it's illegal.
لأنه غير قانوني.
You know exactly how you got the chairman's signature.
أنت تعرف بالضبط كيف حصلت على توقيع الرئيس.
Don't make me laugh.
لا تجعلني أضحك.
Because it was illegal?
لأنه كان غير قانوني؟
That's rich, coming from you, whose whole life is one big scam.
هذا غني، قادم منك، الذي كانت حياته كلها عبارة عن عملية احتيال كبيرة.
Sure, I had to claw my way up from nothing...
بالتأكيد، كان عليّ أن أشق طريقي من الصفر...
and had to do some shady things to survive,
وكان علينا أن نفعل بعض الأشياء المشبوهة من أجل البقاء،
but why are you, born with a silver spoon, so eager to commit a crime?
ولكن لماذا أنت، المولود بملعقة فضية، متلهف لارتكاب جريمة؟
Are you lecturing me right now?
هل أنت تحاضرني الآن؟
You didn't do what you were supposed to, and now you're crying "illegal"?
لم تفعل ما كان من المفترض أن تفعله، والآن تبكي "غير قانوني"؟
Do you have any idea what kind of mess we're in because of you?
هل لديك أي فكرة عن نوع الفوضى التي نحن فيها بسببك؟
That woman, Lucia, is about to inherit my father's entire fortune!
تلك المرأة، لوسيا، على وشك أن ترث ثروة والدي بأكملها!
And he might not even make it through the night!
وربما لا يتمكن حتى من قضاء الليل!
He hasn't passed away yet.
لم يمت بعد
Aren't you getting a little ahead of yourself?
ألا تتقدم على نفسك قليلاً؟
Stop right there.
توقف هنا.
Didn't you hear me? I said stop!
ألم تسمعني؟ قلت توقف!
I'm not someone who stops and goes at your command anymore!
أنا لست شخصًا يتوقف ويذهب بناءً على أوامرك بعد الآن!
Those are commands you give to a dog.
هذه هي الأوامر التي تعطيها للكلب.
From now on, I'll go when I want, and stop when I want.
من الآن فصاعدا، سأذهب عندما أريد، وأتوقف عندما أريد.
No matter who's telling me.
لا يهم من يخبرني.
Especially you.
وخاصة أنت.
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
I'll let go once you calm down.
سأتركك عندما تهدأ.
How dare you...
كيف تجرؤ...
If you keep this up, I can't let you go.
إذا واصلت على هذا المنوال، لن أستطيع أن أتركك.
It's not because I'm afraid you'll hit me.
ليس لأنني خائف من أن تضربني.
It's because I can't bear to watch you humiliate yourself any further.
هذا لأنني لا أستطيع أن أتحمل مشاهدتك تهين نفسك أكثر من ذلك.
Humiliate myself?
أذل نفسي؟
Let's talk about who's really pathetic.
دعونا نتحدث عن من هو مثير للشفقة حقا.
Marrying an old man you don't even love, just to get revenge for your daughter?
الزواج من رجل عجوز لا تحبينه حتى، فقط للانتقام لابنتك؟
Or scheming to take over the company?
أم يخططون للاستيلاء على الشركة؟
Hey! Jung Lucia!
مرحباً! لوسيا الصغيرة!
No, Baek Sul Hee! Don't you dare mess with me!
لا يا بايك سول هي! لا تجرؤ على العبث معي!
I'm the one who made you who you are!
أنا الذي جعلك ما أنت عليه!
Please, don't be like this.
من فضلك لا تكن هكذا.
You and I...
أنت وأنا...
may not be related by blood, but we were more than family.
قد لا نكون مرتبطين بالدم، لكننا كنا أكثر من مجرد عائلة.
I thought of you as a mother,
لقد فكرت فيك كأم،
and I was more heartbroken than anyone over Ho Se's accident.
وكنت أكثر حزنًا من أي شخص آخر بسبب حادث هو سي.
I'm doing this for my Ho Se, too.
أنا أفعل هذا من أجل Ho Se أيضًا.
My son,
ابني
and my only blood relative, Se Ri.
وقريبتي الوحيدة هي سي ري.
I have to protect her! I have to protect her from you!
يجب عليّ حمايتها! يجب عليّ حمايتها منك!
Are we clear?
هل نحن واضحون؟
You little...
أنت صغير...
What do you think you're doing?
ماذا تعتقد أنك تفعل؟
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Why are you falling apart like this? This isn't the person you used to be.
لماذا تنهار هكذا؟ هذا ليس الشخص الذي كنته من قبل.
Please, get a grip!
من فضلك، تمسك بالحكم!
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
What has gotten into Madam Jang now?
ماذا حدث للسيدة جانج الآن؟
She thinks I'm going to do something to harm Se Ri.
إنها تعتقد أنني سأفعل شيئًا لإيذاء سي ري.
If she's going to be like this, why don't we tell her the truth?
إذا كانت ستصبح هكذا، لماذا لا نقول لها الحقيقة؟
But I told you she would go after Se Ri.
ولكنني أخبرتك أنها ستذهب وراء سي ري.
Think about what Se Ri did to Mi So, her own flesh and blood.
فكر في ما فعلته سي ري بمي سو، من لحمها ودمها.
You think Madam Jang would leave Se Ri alone?
هل تعتقد أن السيدة جانج ستترك سي ري بمفردها؟
But how long are we supposed to sit here and take this?
ولكن إلى متى من المفترض أن نجلس هنا ونتحمل هذا؟
This feels like just the beginning, not the end.
يبدو أن هذه مجرد البداية، وليس النهاية.
Still, I won't let Se Ri get hurt. Absolutely not.
مع ذلك، لن أسمح لأري أن تتأذى. قطعًا لا.
Yes, I know. I get it. I feel the same way,
نعم، أعرف. أفهم ذلك. أشعر بنفس الشعور.
but if we let Madam Jang carry on like this,
ولكن إذا سمحنا للسيدة جانج بالاستمرار على هذا النحو،
things are going to get much worse.
الأمور سوف تصبح أسوأ بكثير.
It won't just end with the two of us getting kicked out of this company.
لن ينتهي الأمر فقط بطردنا من هذه الشركة.
Someone could end up getting killed.
قد ينتهي الأمر بشخص ما إلى القتل.
Surely she wouldn't go as far as taking a life.
بالتأكيد لن تصل إلى حد قتل حياة أحد.
After all she's done, you still don't get it?
بعد كل ما فعلته، هل مازلت لا تفهم؟
Madam Jang is not in her right mind right now.
السيدة جانج ليست في حالتها الصحيحة الآن.
She's going to take out her anger for her son on Chairman Min Doo Sik,
إنها ستفرغ غضبها على ابنها على رئيس مجلس الإدارة مين دو سيك،
and if she thinks anyone is a threat to Se Ri's future,
وإذا كانت تعتقد أن أي شخص يشكل تهديدًا لمستقبل سي ري،
she'll try to eliminate them by any means necessary.
ستحاول القضاء عليهم بأي وسيلة ممكنة.
We have to stop Madam Jang's rampage.
علينا أن نوقف هجوم السيدة جانج.
I know, but the problem is we don't know how.
أنا أعلم، لكن المشكلة هي أننا لا نعرف كيف.
Even Min Kyung Chae is at a complete loss when facing her.
حتى مين كيونغ تشاي تشعر بالحيرة التامة عندما تواجهها.
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
(CEO Min Kyung Chae)
(الرئيس التنفيذي مين كيونغ تشاي)
Mother, it's me. Kyung Chae.
أمي، أنا كيونغ تشاي.
Mother.
الأم.
What's wrong? Are you hurt somewhere?
ما الأمر؟ هل أنت مصاب في مكان ما؟
That Lucia, she...
تلك لوسيا، هي...
What about Lucia?
ماذا عن لوسيا؟
What about her?
ماذا عنها؟
You don't even know what's going on with Se Ri?
أنت لا تعرف حتى ما يحدث مع سي ري؟
And you call yourself her mother?
وتسمي نفسك أمها؟
Se Ri's at home, of course.
سي ري في المنزل، بالطبع.
Lucia got Se Ri a job at a cafe as a waitress...
حصلت لوسيا على وظيفة لسي ري في مقهى كنادلة ...
for a measly ten dollars an hour.
مقابل عشرة دولارات فقط في الساعة.
What?
ماذا؟
Why would she do that?
لماذا تفعل ذلك؟
Lucia is making Se Ri suffer since she's not her real daughter.
لوسيا تجعل سي ري تعاني لأنها ليست ابنتها الحقيقية.
And there are so many creeps out there these days.
وهناك الكثير من الزواحف هناك هذه الأيام.
What if she gets a difficult customer,
ماذا لو حصلت على عميل صعب؟
gets into an argument, and things get violent?
يدخل في جدال ويصبح الأمر عنيفًا؟
What then?
ماذا بعد؟
Why won't you listen to me?
لماذا لا تستمع لي؟
I told you I'd take Se Ri to the States and put her through college!
لقد أخبرتك أنني سآخذ سي ري إلى الولايات المتحدة وأرسلها إلى الكلية!
You haven't even told Se Ri yet, have you?
لم تخبر سي ري بعد، أليس كذلك؟
And you still expect my help?
ومازلت تتوقع مساعدتي؟
It's just that...
إنه فقط ذلك...
I've had a lot on my mind lately.
لقد كان هناك الكثير في ذهني في الآونة الأخيرة.
What are you preoccupied with?
بماذا تشغل بالك؟
Lawyer Kim still hasn't filed the divorce papers...
المحامي كيم لم يقدم أوراق الطلاق بعد
for Lucia and Dad.
للوسيا وأبي.
What?
ماذا؟
What is it now?
ما هو الآن؟
Min Kyung Chae found out everything today.
مين كيونغ تشاي عرفت كل شيء اليوم.
That you and Min Doo Sik are still legally married,
أنك ومين دو سيك لا تزالان متزوجين قانونيًا،
and that I never filed the papers.
وأنني لم أقدم الأوراق أبدًا.
(Chairman Min Doo Sik)
(الرئيس مين دو سيك)
And you're still hanging around? Shouldn't you be on the run?
وما زلتَ قاب قوسين أو أدنى؟ ألا يجب عليكَ الهرب؟
No. You won't find paradise by running away.
لا، لن تجد الجنة بالهروب.
This is my paradise, the one I'm going to build right here.
هذه هي جنتي، التي سأبنيها هنا.
Trashing the divorce papers might've bought us time,
ربما كان التخلص من أوراق الطلاق قد يمنحنا بعض الوقت،
but if Min Kyung Chae proposes my dismissal at the shareholders' meeting,
ولكن إذا اقترح مين كيونج تشاي إقالتي في اجتماع المساهمين،
it'll pass.
سوف يمر.
It won't be that easy for her.
لن يكون الأمر سهلاً بالنسبة لها.
If I give you all my secretly held shares,
إذا أعطيتك كل أسهمي التي أحتفظ بها سراً،
not even the great Min Kyung Chae can touch us.
حتى مين كيونغ تشاي العظيمة لا تستطيع أن تلمسنا.
You're starting to scare me when you're like this.
أنت تبدأ في إخافتي عندما تكون هكذا.
Seriously, what has gotten into you?
بجدية، ما الذي أصابك؟
I told you. This is my paradise.
لقد قلت لك، هذه جنتي.
I want a fresh start with you and Se Ri.
أريد بداية جديدة معك ومع سي ري.
What reason could be clearer than that?
ما السبب الذي قد يكون أوضح من ذلك؟
(Chairman Min Doo Sik)
(الرئيس مين دو سيك)
Sul Hee.
سول هي.
The past is in the past.
الماضي في الماضي.
Do you think I took off my engagement ring to Min Kyung Chae lightly?
هل تعتقد أنني خلعت خاتم خطوبتي لمين كيونج تشاي بسهولة؟
No. For me, it was like starting a new life.
لا، بالنسبة لي كان الأمر بمثابة بدء حياة جديدة.
I'm doing things my way for my life and the remaining years.
أنا أفعل الأشياء بطريقتي في حياتي والسنوات المتبقية.
My new beginning includes Baek Sul Hee and Kim Se Ri.
بدايتي الجديدة تتضمن بايك سول هي وكيم سي ري.
Anyway, just keep that in mind.
على أية حال، فقط ضع ذلك في الاعتبار.
No one can touch us, not even the shareholders' meeting.
لا أحد يستطيع المساس بنا، حتى اجتماع المساهمين.
We'll get through this together as a family.
سوف نتجاوز هذا الأمر معًا كعائلة.
Okay?
تمام؟
Come on. We've got this!
هيا، لقد حصلنا على هذا!
(Chairman Min Doo Sik)
(الرئيس مين دو سيك)
Seriously...
بجد...
So you knew the divorce papers were never filed.
لذا فأنت تعلم أن أوراق الطلاق لم يتم تقديمها أبدًا.
Does that mean you were conspiring with Lawyer Kim?
هل هذا يعني أنك كنت متآمرًا مع المحامي كيم؟
It wasn't a conspiracy. It was the right thing to do.
لم تكن مؤامرة، بل كان القرار الصائب.
Forcing a thumbprint from an unconscious man...
إجبار رجل فاقد الوعي على أخذ بصمة الإبهام
is a serious crime.
تعتبر جريمة خطيرة.
You should be grateful that Lawyer Kim's judgment...
يجب أن تكون ممتنًا لحكم المحامي كيم ...
prevented something terrible.
منعت شيئا فظيعا.
Now that you know I am still legally Chairman Min Doo Sik's wife,
الآن بعد أن عرفت أنني لا أزال قانونيًا زوجة رئيس مجلس الإدارة مين دو سيك،
you're going to tell me where he is, right?
أنت ستخبرني أين هو، أليس كذلك؟
As his legal spouse,
بصفته زوجته القانونية،
don't I have the right to know where my husband is and how he's doing?
أليس من حقي أن أعرف أين زوجي وكيف حاله؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
He's in a good place and well cared for.
إنه في مكان جيد ويتم الاهتمام به جيدًا.
I need to see that for myself.
أريد أن أرى ذلك بنفسي.
If you don't tell me right now, I have no choice...
إذا لم تخبرني الآن، فلن يكون لدي خيار...
but to call the police.
ولكن لاستدعاء الشرطة.
- You'll what? - It's the only way I can find him.
- ماذا ستفعل؟ - هذه هي الطريقة الوحيدة التي أستطيع من خلالها العثور عليه.
You know it'll be a missing person case if his wife reports it, right?
أنت تعلم أن هذه ستكون قضية شخص مفقود إذا أبلغت زوجته عنها، أليس كذلك؟
Ja Kyung hasn't called lately. I wonder if something's wrong.
لم يتصل جا كيونغ مؤخرًا. أتساءل إن كان هناك خطب ما.
She's not calling because there's nothing going on.
إنها لا تتصل لأنه لا يوجد شيء يحدث.
No news is good news, you know.
لا يوجد خبر، فهو خبر جيد، كما تعلم.
This much "no news" can't be good news.
هذا القدر من "عدم وجود أخبار" لا يمكن أن يكون أخبارًا جيدة.
For a mother, you don't have a shred of maternal instinct.
بالنسبة للأم، ليس لديك ذرة من غريزة الأمومة.
I heard that Ja Kyung's young mother-in-law...
سمعت أن حمات جا كيونغ الشابة...
dotes on Se Ri as if she were her own...
تحب سي ري كما لو كانت ابنتها.
when she didn't even give birth to her.
عندما لم تلدها بعد.
I always thought that was a bit strange.
اعتقدت دائمًا أن هذا كان غريبًا بعض الشيء.
Let's be honest, that girl is hardly an angel.
دعونا نكون صادقين، هذه الفتاة ليست ملاكًا على الإطلاق.
She's a bit of a handful, isn't she? Though she has been quiet lately.
إنها صعبة المراس بعض الشيء، أليس كذلك؟ مع أنها كانت هادئة مؤخرًا.
She was quite the troublemaker, all on her own, wasn't she?
لقد كانت مثيرة للمشاكل إلى حد كبير، بمفردها، أليس كذلك؟
That's what makes this so amazing, right?
هذا ما يجعل الأمر مدهشًا جدًا، أليس كذلك؟
They're just mother and daughter on paper, not by blood, but they dote on each other.
إنهم مجرد أم وابنتها على الورق، وليس عن طريق الدم، لكنهم يحبون بعضهم البعض.
Exactly. Fawning over her like that isn't normal.
بالضبط. التملق لها بهذه الطريقة ليس طبيعيًا.
Even your own kids can drive you up the wall sometimes,
حتى أطفالك قد يزعجونك أحيانًا،
so it makes no sense to act like that with someone else's child.
لذلك لا معنى للتصرف بهذه الطريقة مع طفل شخص آخر.
Not unless there's some secret no one knows about.
ليس إلا إذا كان هناك سر لا أحد يعرفه.
What kind of secret?
ما هو نوع السر؟
What if Se Ri is actually Chairman Min's wife's long-lost daughter?
ماذا لو كانت سي ري في الواقع هي الابنة المفقودة منذ فترة طويلة لزوجة الرئيس مين؟
Something like that.
شيئ من هذا القبيل.
Are you writing a soap opera?
هل تكتب مسلسلا تلفزيونيا؟
You come up with absurd secret origins because you watch them all day.
تتوصل إلى أصول سرية سخيفة لأنك تشاهدها طوال اليوم.
Why stop there? Let's make it juicier.
لماذا نتوقف عند هذا الحد؟ لنجعل الأمر أكثر إثارة.
Tae Kyung and our in-laws are enemies,
تاي كيونغ وأصهارنا أعداء،
Kyung Chae is Ms. Stella's daughter-in-law,
كيونغ تشاي هي زوجة ابن السيدة ستيلا،
and Sun Jae is Se Ri's biological father.
وسون جاي هو الأب البيولوجي لسي ري.
Want to take this soap even further? Ji Seop is Manager Gong's son,
هل ترغب في تطوير هذا المسلسل أكثر؟ جي سوب هو ابن المدير غونغ.
Ja Kyung isn't my biological daughter, Tae Kyung is my son,
جا كيونغ ليست ابنتي البيولوجية، تاي كيونغ هو ابني،
but they were switched at birth.
ولكن تم تبديلهم عند الولادة.
And for the grand finale of this mess,
وللنهاية الكبرى لهذه الفوضى،
Chairman Min Doo Sik and I are half-brothers. Happy now?
أنا والرئيس مين دو سيك أخوان غير شقيقين. هل أنتم سعداء الآن؟
That's hilarious.
هذا مضحك.
It is? Maybe I should be a scriptwriter.
أهي كذلك؟ ربما عليّ أن أكون كاتب سيناريو.
- Whatever. Just call Ja Kyung. - See? Over-the-top dramas are the best.
- لا بأس. اتصل بجا كيونغ. - أرأيت؟ المسلسلات المبالغ فيها هي الأفضل.
Ja Kyung?
جا كيونغ؟
No, nothing's wrong. Your dad just wanted me to call.
لا، لا مشكلة. والدك أراد مني فقط أن أتصل.
Please. As if anything exciting happens with us.
من فضلك. كما لو أن شيئًا مثيرًا يحدث معنا.
Right now, all we can think about is Ji Seop's promotion.
في الوقت الحالي، كل ما يمكننا التفكير فيه هو ترقية جي سوب.
But you said that was happening soon.
لكنك قلت أن هذا سيحدث قريبا.
I thought it was a done deal.
اعتقدت أن الأمر قد تم.
It is, but I won't be able to relax until it's official.
إنه كذلك، ولكن لن أتمكن من الاسترخاء حتى يصبح الأمر رسميًا.
Of course he'll get it. If not Ji Seop, who else would?
بالتأكيد سيحصل عليه. إن لم يكن جي سوب، فمن سيحصل عليه؟
He will, right?
إنه سيفعل ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Mom, I'll call you back tomorrow.
أمي سأتصل بك غدًا.
Your parents will be so disappointed if I don't become a director.
سوف يشعر والديك بخيبة أمل كبيرة إذا لم أصبح مخرجًا.
They're counting on it so much.
إنهم يعتمدون عليه كثيرا.
Hey, don't jinx it. Why would you say that?
مهلا، لا تجلب الحظ السيئ. لماذا تقول هذا؟
I don't know, it's just...
لا أعلم، إنه فقط...
the days are just ticking by, and the appointments are getting closer,
الأيام تمر بسرعة، والمواعيد تقترب،
so I'm just getting a little anxious.
لذا فأنا أشعر بالقلق قليلاً.
Don't be. You should've been a director ages ago.
لا تكن كذلك. كان ينبغي أن تصبح مخرجًا منذ زمن طويل.
And it's not like it's some gift.
وليس الأمر وكأنه هدية.
We're handing over all of our shares for you to get that position.
نحن نسلم لك جميع أسهمنا لتتمكن من الحصول على هذا المنصب.
But what will happen to Soo Jung if I take over her position?
ولكن ماذا سيحدث لسو جونغ إذا توليت منصبها؟
What kind of ridiculous nonsense is that?
ما هذا النوع من الهراء السخيف؟
Who's worrying about whom?
من يقلق على من؟
You're the most pathetic of the Min family.
أنت الأكثر إثارة للشفقة في عائلة مين.
You're the weakest.
أنت الأضعف.
If you only knew.
لو كنت تعلم فقط.
- The doors are closing. - Hold on, please!
-الأبواب تغلق. -انتظر من فضلك!
Thank you...
شكرًا لك...
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
The doors are closing.
الأبواب تغلق.
The second you walked through the entrance,
في الثانية التي دخلت فيها من المدخل،
you were radiant.
لقد كنت متألقا.
What are you on about this early in the morning?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه في هذا الصباح الباكر؟
You just have this way of standing out, no matter where you are.
لديك هذه الطريقة للتميز، بغض النظر عن مكان وجودك.
Twenty-five years ago,
منذ خمسة وعشرين عامًا،
do you know why I chose you out of all the women...
هل تعلم لماذا اخترتك من بين كل النساء...
who were throwing themselves at me?
من كانوا يرمون أنفسهم علي؟
It's because you were so incredibly beautiful.
هذا لأنك كنت جميلة بشكل لا يصدق.
Why are you so jumpy?
لماذا أنت متوترة جداً؟
A stray hair.
شعرة ضالة.
Seriously...
بجد...
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
Does my touch still give you an electric jolt?
هل لا تزال لمستي تمنحك صدمة كهربائية؟
The first time we slept together,
في المرة الأولى التي نمنا فيها معًا،
you were the same way then.
لقد كنت بنفس الطريقة حينها.
Shut up! You're such a pervert. Seriously!
اسكت! أنت منحرف جدًا. بجد!
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
Unbelievable.
لا يصدق.
Why are you following me?
لماذا تتبعني؟
If you keep this up, I'm calling Tae Kyung.
إذا واصلت على هذا المنوال، سأتصل بتاي كيونغ.
You need to stop.
يجب عليك التوقف.
If I'm making an effort, you should meet me halfway.
إذا كنت أبذل جهدًا، فيجب أن تقابلني في منتصف الطريق.
Do you think I let that punk hit me because I'm weak?
هل تعتقد أنني سمحت لهذا الوغد بضربي لأنني ضعيف؟
No. If I got serious, I could take him out with one punch.
لا، إذا كنت جادًا، يمكنني التخلص منه بلكمة واحدة.
I felt bad for his pathetic life, so I let him win.
لقد شعرت بالأسف تجاه حياته البائسة، لذلك تركته يفوز.
Seriously, what is wrong with you?
بجدية، ما الخطأ معك؟
Now that you know Se Ri is our daughter,
الآن بعد أن عرفت أن سي ري هي ابنتنا،
you've suddenly had some life-changing epiphany?
هل حصلت فجأة على بعض الأفكار التي غيرت حياتك؟
Of course I did. I haven't been this happy in a long time,
بالطبع فعلت. لم أكن سعيدًا هكذا منذ زمن طويل.
thinking about messing over Min Kyung Chae and the rest of the Min family...
أفكر في العبث مع مين كيونج تشاي وبقية أفراد عائلة مين...
For goodness' sake, snap out of it!
من أجل الخير، حاول التخلص من هذا الأمر!
Fine. You're Se Ri's father, so I'll put up with this much.
حسنًا. أنت والد سي ري، لذا سأتحمل هذا القدر.
But if you cross that line, I can't promise what I'll do.
ولكن إذا تجاوزت هذا الخط، لا أستطيع أن أعدك بما سأفعله.
And what exactly are you going to do to me?
وماذا ستفعل بي بالضبط؟
(CEO Min Kyung Chae)
(الرئيس التنفيذي مين كيونغ تشاي)
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
He always stopped by around this time.
لقد كان يتوقف دائمًا في هذا الوقت.
(CEO Min Kyung Chae)
(الرئيس التنفيذي مين كيونغ تشاي)
Seriously! This is Min Kyung Chae's problem.
جدياً! هذه مشكلة مين كيونغ تشاي.
She just wears you out.
إنها فقط تستنزف طاقتك.
A woman should be more like you, you know?
ينبغي للمرأة أن تكون أكثر شبهاً بك، هل تعلم؟
She should play hard to get a little. Right?
يجب عليها أن تلعب بجدية للحصول على القليل. أليس كذلك؟
Just go already.
فقط اذهب بالفعل.
I told you if you keep this up, I'll have no choice, right?
لقد قلت لك إذا واصلت هذا الأمر، فلن يكون لدي خيار، أليس كذلك؟
Yes, so?
نعم إذن؟
What are you going to do to me? Go on, tell me.
ماذا ستفعل بي؟ هيا، أخبرني.
I'm curious myself.
أنا فضولي بنفسي.
You're curious?
هل أنت فضولي؟
Of course I am.
بالطبع أنا كذلك.
My girl says she has something in store for me.
تقول ابنتي أنها لديها شيئًا في المتجر بالنسبة لي.
All right, then.
حسنا إذن.
Meet me on the rooftop after work.
قابليني على سطح المنزل بعد العمل.
Now I'm excited.
الآن أنا متحمس.
Wait a second.
انتظر ثانية.
Is this about that kiss that didn't happen last time?
هل يتعلق الأمر بتلك القبلة التي لم تحدث في المرة الماضية؟
That's it, right?
هذا هو الأمر، أليس كذلك؟
I knew it. How could you possibly resist me?
كنت أعرف ذلك. كيف يمكنك مقاومتي؟
I look forward to it, Baek Sul Hee. See you later. Okay?
أتطلع إلى ذلك، بايك سول هي. أراك لاحقًا. حسنًا؟
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
(CEO Min Kyung Chae)
(الرئيس التنفيذي مين كيونغ تشاي)
Why didn't you answer my call?
لماذا لم تجيب على مكالمتي؟
Because I thought I couldn't deal with you.
لأنني اعتقدت أنني لا أستطيع التعامل معك.
What did you just say?
ماذا قلت للتو؟
Who do you think you're talking to like that?
من تعتقد أنك تتحدث معه بهذه الطريقة؟
We're engaged. Is it such a big deal if I drop the formalities?
نحن مخطوبان. هل يُزعجني أن أتخلى عن الرسميات؟
Do you have any idea what I'm going through right now?
هل لديك أي فكرة عما أمر به الآن؟
That woman, Lucia, basically declared war on me yesterday.
لقد أعلنت تلك المرأة، لوسيا، الحرب عليّ بالأمس.
She said she would call the cops if I didn't tell her where my father is.
قالت إنها سوف تتصل بالشرطة إذا لم أخبرها بمكان والدي.
So?
لذا؟
"So?"
"لذا؟"
You can't act like this at a time like this, Lawyer Kim.
لا يمكنك التصرف بهذه الطريقة في وقت كهذا، المحامي كيم.
Then how should I be acting?
إذن كيف يجب أن أتصرف؟
What on earth is wrong with you?
ما الذي حدث لك على الأرض؟
You wouldn't act like this without a reason.
لن تتصرف بهذه الطريقة بدون سبب.
Did I do something to upset you?
هل فعلت شيئا أزعجك؟
When you took off your engagement ring, I thought you wanted to break up.
عندما خلعت خاتم خطوبتك، اعتقدت أنك تريد الانفصال.
Then, did you ever actually plan to marry me?
إذن، هل كنت تخطط فعليا للزواج مني؟
- What are you talking about... - Answer me.
- عن ماذا تتحدث... - أجبني.
I'm asking if you were actually going to marry me.
أنا أسأل إذا كنت فعلا تنوي الزواج بي.
And you have the nerve...
و لديك الشجاعة...
If she reports you, then so be it.
إذا أبلغت عنك، فليكن.
If you don't like that, then just tell her where the chairman is.
إذا لم يعجبك ذلك، فما عليك إلا أن تخبرها بمكان الرئيس.
(CEO Min Kyung Chae)
(الرئيس التنفيذي مين كيونغ تشاي)
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
No...
لا...
- Excuse me, can I get some water? - Water is self-serve.
- عذراً، هل يمكنني الحصول على بعض الماء؟ - الماء يخدم نفسه بنفسه.
I can't believe this.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق هذا.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
How did you find me here?
كيف وجدتني هنا؟
Can't you see? I'm working.
ألا ترى؟ أنا أعمل.
Anyone seeing this would think you're the breadwinner.
أي شخص يرى هذا سوف يعتقد أنك أنت المعيل.
Who told you to go out and earn money?
من قال لك أن تخرج وتكسب المال؟
It's none of your business what I do!
إنه ليس من شأنك ما أفعله!
If you came for coffee, find a seat and order one.
إذا أتيت لتناول القهوة، ابحث عن مقعد واطلب واحدة.
You're going to keep working here even if I tell you to stop, aren't you?
ستستمر في العمل هنا حتى لو طلبت منك التوقف، أليس كذلك؟
What if your stepmother tells you to quit?
ماذا لو طلبت منك زوجة أبيك أن تتوقف؟
- Well, that's... - Really?
- حسنًا، هذا... - حقًا؟
Then just you wait.
ثم عليك فقط الانتظار.
Hey. You'll never guess where I am right now.
مهلا، لن تخمن أبدًا أين أنا الآن.
Our Se Ri is here, waiting tables.
سي ري لدينا هنا، يخدم الطاولات.
I can't stand watching her slaving away like this for ten dollars an hour.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل مشاهدتها تعمل بهذا الشكل مقابل عشرة دولارات في الساعة.
What should we do about this?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل حيال هذا؟
She's not doing it for the money, so please just leave her be.
إنها لا تفعل ذلك من أجل المال، لذا من فضلك اتركها وشأنها.
You can't be this callous just because she's not your own blood.
لا يمكنك أن تكون قاسي القلب إلى هذا الحد لمجرد أنها ليست من دمك.
What on earth does she lack to have to work here?
ما الذي ينقصها حتى تعمل هنا؟
It's a life lesson.
إنه درس الحياة.
She will learn how to get along with all sorts of people.
ستتعلم كيفية التعامل مع جميع أنواع الناس.
That's ridiculous.
هذا سخيف.
I can teach her about life myself. She doesn't need to learn it here.
أستطيع أن أعلمها الحياة بنفسي. لا داعي لتعلمها هنا.
I'm putting her on the phone. Tell her to quit this instant.
سأتصل بها. أخبرها أن تتوقف فورًا.
Or maybe I should tell her...
أو ربما يجب أن أخبرها...
everything I know about Lucia. Get my drift?
كل ما أعرفه عن لوسيا. هل فهمت قصدي؟
Here. Your stepmother wants to talk to you.
هنا. زوجة أبيك تريد التحدث معك.
Mom, you wanted to talk?
أمي هل تريدين التحدث؟
Se Ri. Don't pay her any mind. Just keep working.
سي ري. لا تُعرها أي اهتمام. استمر في العمل.
Learn how hard it is to earn your own money...
تعرف على مدى صعوبة كسب المال الخاص بك...
and learn how to get along with the people you work with.
وتعلم كيفية التعامل مع الأشخاص الذين تعمل معهم.
You can do that, can't you?
يمكنك فعل ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Yes. I'll see you at home later.
نعم سأراك في المنزل لاحقًا.
She told you to quit, right?
لقد طلبت منك الإستقالة، أليس كذلك؟
See? Why are you wasting your time with this?
أرأيت؟ لماذا تضيع وقتك بهذا؟
Take that apron off and come with me.
اخلع هذا المئزر وتعالى معي.
I needed to talk to you today anyway.
كنت بحاجة للتحدث معك اليوم على أية حال.
- About going to college in the States... - If you're not ordering, please leave.
- بخصوص الذهاب إلى الكلية في الولايات المتحدة... - إذا كنت لا تطلب، يرجى المغادرة.
I have to finish my shift.
يجب علي أن أنهي نوبتي.
That's what Mom told me to do.
هذا ما قالته لي أمي.
It'll take more than a glass of water to calm me down.
سيستغرق الأمر أكثر من كوب من الماء لتهدئتي.
Are you really that upset?
هل أنت منزعج حقا؟
Lucia was just trying to do what was best for Se Ri.
كانت لوسيا تحاول فقط أن تفعل ما هو الأفضل لسي ري.
How is that for her own good? It's not like she needs the money.
كيف يكون هذا لصالحها؟ ليس كأنها بحاجة للمال.
Why is she working a part-time job in some random cafe?
لماذا تعمل بدوام جزئي في أحد المقاهي العشوائية؟
That's what a lot of kids her age do.
هذا ما يفعله الكثير من الأطفال في سنها.
- It's perfectly normal. - No. My Se Ri is special.
- إنه أمر طبيعي تمامًا. - لا. سي ري خاصتي.
Because she is my son Ho Se's daughter.
لأنها ابنة ابني هو سي.
The girl who will one day own Mingang, serving coffee?
الفتاة التي ستمتلك يوما ما مينغانغ، وتقدم القهوة؟
Mother.
الأم.
You've changed so much since you found out Se Ri is Ho Se's daughter.
لقد تغيرت كثيرًا منذ أن اكتشفت أن سي ري هي ابنة هو سي.
Of course I changed!
بالطبع لقد تغيرت!
She's my grandchild. Am I not supposed to look after her?
إنها حفيدتي. ألا يُفترض بي أن أعتني بها؟
You're going overboard.
أنت تذهب إلى أبعد من الحد.
I'm worried you're going to get hurt if you keep this up.
أنا قلق من أنك سوف تتأذى إذا واصلت هذا.
Don't you worry about me. I'm Stella Jang.
لا تقلق عليّ. أنا ستيلا جانج.
Do you know what it took for me to survive in the States?
هل تعلم ما الذي كان علي أن أفعله حتى أتمكن من البقاء على قيد الحياة في الولايات المتحدة؟
Mother.
الأم.
Lucia says she's going to report me to the police...
تقول لوسيا أنها سوف تبلغ عني للشرطة...
if I don't tell her where Father is.
إذا لم أخبرها أين أبي.
Since that snake Kim Sun Jae betrayed us, this could all come to nothing.
منذ أن خاننا ذلك الثعبان كيم سون جاي، كل هذا قد لا يؤدي إلى شيء.
After all we went through to get those divorce papers.
بعد كل ما مررنا به للحصول على أوراق الطلاق.
What are we going to do?
ماذا سنفعل؟
If shareholders learn of Father's health, the acting chairmanship will be extended.
إذا علم المساهمون بصحة الأب، فسيتم تمديد رئاسة مجلس الإدارة بالنيابة.
And if things go wrong,
وإذا سارت الأمور على نحو خاطئ،
the chairmanship could be passed on to her permanently.
ويمكن أن تنتقل إليها الرئاسة بشكل دائم.
I was only appointed to this position without the board's approval.
لقد تم تعييني في هذا المنصب دون موافقة مجلس الإدارة.
But she went through the proper channels to get hers.
لكنها ذهبت عبر القنوات المناسبة للحصول على ما تريد.
So Kim Sun Jae has sided with Lucia, is that it?
إذن كيم سون جاي قد انحاز إلى جانب لوسيا، أليس كذلك؟
He realized he had no shot at marrying Min Kyung Chae,
أدرك أنه ليس لديه فرصة للزواج من مين كيونغ تشاي،
so he switched sides?
فهل تحول إلى الجانب الآخر؟
What do I do, Mother?
ماذا أفعل يا أمي؟
Just be quiet for a second. I'm trying to think.
فقط اصمت لثانية واحدة. أحاول أن أفكر.
It's so quiet. I guess everyone's gone home for the day.
إنه هادئ جدًا. أعتقد أن الجميع عادوا إلى منازلهم لهذا اليوم.
There's no one else in the office.
لا يوجد أحد آخر في المكتب.
It feels like we're the only two people in the world.
نشعر وكأننا الشخصان الوحيدان في العالم.
Tae Kyung.
تاي كيونغ.
Yes?
نعم؟
Kim Sun Jae is on his way up.
كيم سون جاي في طريقه إلى الأعلى.
I asked him to come.
طلبت منه أن يأتي.
I need to make...
أحتاج إلى أن أصنع...
my feelings perfectly clear in front of him.
مشاعري واضحة تماما أمامه.
Your feelings?
مشاعرك؟
What are the three of us supposed to do now?
ماذا ينبغي لنا الثلاثة أن نفعل الآن؟
What, are we going to get into a fistfight like last time?
ماذا، هل سندخل في عراك بالأيدي مثل المرة السابقة؟
Kim Sun Jae.
كيم سون جاي.
I need you to listen very carefully to what I'm about to say.
أريدك أن تستمع بعناية شديدة لما سأقوله.
I...
أنا...
am in love with Moon Tae Kyung.
أنا في حب مون تاي كيونغ.
You being Se Ri's biological father means nothing to me.
كونك الأب البيولوجي لـ Se Ri لا يعني شيئًا بالنسبة لي.
There's no way I'm starting over with you for a pathetic reason like that.
لا أستطيع أن أبدأ معك من جديد لسبب مثير للشفقة مثل هذا.
You may have been my first, but that doesn't mean you'll be the last.
ربما كنت الأول بالنسبة لي، لكن هذا لا يعني أنك ستكون الأخير.
The last man for me...
الرجل الأخير بالنسبة لي...
is him.
هو هو.
So, just give it up.
لذا، فقط استسلم.
Stop using Se Ri as an excuse to force your way into our lives.
توقف عن استخدام سي ري كذريعة لفرض طريقك إلى حياتنا.
Are you out of your mind?
هل أنت خارج عقلك؟
I've never been more clear-headed. Now go! Get lost!
لم أكن يومًا أكثر صفاءً ذهنيًا. الآن انطلق! ابتعد!
Get out of my life and my sight!
إخرج من حياتي ومن نظري!
You've completely lost it.
لقد فقدتها تماما.
You're nothing without me.
أنت لا شيء بدوني.
Right now, I'm your savior, your deity.
الآن، أنا منقذك، إلهك.
Without me, you'll go down in flames and hit rock bottom.
بدوني سوف تغرق في النيران وتصل إلى القاع.
Let me spell it out.
دعني أوضح ذلك.
If the shareholder's meeting is held, you'll be fired.
إذا تم عقد اجتماع المساهمين، سيتم طردك.
I'll take care of it. I don't need your help, so go!
سأعتني بالأمر. لا أحتاج مساعدتك، لذا اذهب!
How dare you...
كيف تجرؤ...
Back when I didn't know any better,
عندما لم أكن أعرف أي شيء أفضل،
I met you and ended up having your child.
لقد التقيت بك وانتهى بي الأمر بإنجاب طفلك.
Then you abandoned me.
ثم تركتني.
At the time, I was heartbroken and thought my life was over.
في ذلك الوقت، شعرت بالحزن الشديد واعتقدت أن حياتي قد انتهت.
But not anymore.
ولكن ليس بعد الآن.
In fact, I think it was a blessing in disguise.
في الواقع، أعتقد أنها كانت نعمة مقنعة.
You...
أنت...
want our Se Ri to be the third-generation chairman, don't you?
هل تريد أن يكون سي ري هو الرئيس من الجيل الثالث؟
Not a chance.
لا توجد فرصة.
I am never going to let that happen.
لن أسمح بحدوث ذلك أبدًا.
I'm going to raise our Se Ri...
سأرفع سي ري الخاص بنا...
to have a perfectly normal life.
أن أحظى بحياة طبيعية تمامًا.
I won't let her be a monster like you, consumed by your ambition and greed.
لن أسمح لها أن تكون وحشًا مثلك، مستهلكًا بطموحك وجشعك.
So, just go.
إذن فقط اذهب.
If Kim Sun Jae abandoned Baek Sul Hee 20 years ago,
إذا تخلى كيم سون جاي عن بايك سول هي منذ 20 عامًا،
today, it's Baek Sul Hee...
اليوم، إنه بايك سول هي...
who is abandoning Kim Sun Jae.
من يتخلى عن كيم سون جاي؟
Sul Hee.
سول هي.
I never knew you were so brave.
لم أكن أعلم أنك شجاع إلى هذا الحد.
There's more you don't know about me.
هناك المزيد الذي لا تعرفه عني.
I've wanted to tell you...
لقد أردت أن أخبرك...
that I loved you a long time ago.
أنني أحببتك منذ زمن طويل.
Baek Sul Hee.
بايك سول هي.
So this is how you want to play?
إذن هذه هي الطريقة التي تريد أن تلعب بها؟
Fine.
بخير.
Then the gloves are off.
ثم يتم خلع القفازات.
You may not be happy to see me, but that can't be helped.
ربما لا تكون سعيدًا برؤيتي، لكن هذا أمر لا يمكن مساعدته.
I'm here today to tell you something you need to hear.
أنا هنا اليوم لأخبركم بشيء تحتاجون إلى سماعه.
And what is it that I need to hear?
وما الذي أريد أن أسمعه؟
I don't think I can say this sober.
لا أعتقد أنني أستطيع أن أقول هذا بصراحة.
Se Ri...
سي ري...
is not your granddaughter.
ليست حفيدتك.
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Min Kyung Chae's daughter, Min Se Ri. Wait, she's not a Min.
ابنة مين كيونغ تشاي، مين سي ري. لحظة، هي ليست مين.
Her real name is Kim Se Ri.
اسمها الحقيقي هو كيم سي ري.
She is Baek Sul Hee's daughter.
إنها ابنة بايك سول هي.
Which means...
وهذا يعني...
Se Ri's father is not your son. Understand?
والد سي ري ليس ابنك. هل فهمت؟
And I bet you're wondering why her last name is Kim.
وأنا أراهن أنك تتساءل لماذا اسمها الأخير هو كيم.
Because she's my daughter.
لأنها ابنتي.
The daughter of Kim Sun Jae.
ابنة كيم سون جاي.
(The Woman Who Swallowed the Sun)
(المرأة التي ابتلعت الشمس)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)
(يتم توفير الترجمة بواسطة KOCOWA.)